[
  {
  "qId": 1,
  "question": "Who invented Design ?",
  "options": ["Smith", "Bob"],
  "answer": "Smith"
  },

  {
    "qId": 2,
    "question": "Who designed Facebook ?",
    "options": ["Tom","Smith"],
    "answer": "Smith"
  },

  {
    "qId": 3,
    "question": "Who was the first designer recruited by ThoughtWorks ?",
    "options": ["Somya","Ruchi"],
    "answer": "Ruchi"
  },

  {
    "qId": 4,
    "question": "Who invented Design ?",
    "options": ["Smith", "Bob"],
    "answer": "Smith"
  },

  {
    "qId": 5,
    "question": "Who designed Facebook ?",
    "options": ["Tom","Smith"],
    "answer": "Smith"
  },

  {
    "qId": 6,
    "question": "Who was the first designer recruited by ThoughtWorks ?",
    "options": ["Somya","Ruchi"],
    "answer": "Ruchi"
  },

  {
    "qId": 7,
    "question": "Who invented Design ?",
    "options": ["Smith", "Bob"],
    "answer": "Smith"
  },

  {
    "qId": 8,
    "question": "Who designed Facebook ?",
    "options": ["Tom","Smith"],
    "answer": "Smith"
  },

  {
    "qId": 9,
    "question": "Who was the first designer recruited by ThoughtWorks ?",
    "options": ["Somya","Ruchi"],
    "answer": "Ruchi"
  },

  {
    "qId": 10,
    "question": "Who invented Design ?",
    "options": ["Smith", "Bob"],
    "answer": "Smith"
  },

  {
    "qId": 11,
    "question": "Who designed Facebook ?",
    "options": ["Tom","Smith"],
    "answer": "Smith"
  },

  {
    "qId": 12,
    "question": "Who was the first designer recruited by ThoughtWorks ?",
    "options": ["Somya","Ruchi"],
    "answer": "Ruchi"
  }



]
